Finding Aid for the Irene Haupt Photographs of June in Buffalo, 2015
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0910.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_283.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Slee.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_284.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name good.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_285.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0924.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_286.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0929.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_287.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0930.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_288.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0931.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_289.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0932.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_290.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0933.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_291.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0934.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_292.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0935.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_293.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0938.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_294.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0939.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_295.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0940.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_296.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0941.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_297.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0942.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_298.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0948.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_299.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0949.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_300.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0951.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_301.tif)
- One image from Olivier Pasquet's video accompanying David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux performed at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0952.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_302.tif)
- One image from Olivier Pasquet's video accompanying David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux performed at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0953.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_303.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0956.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_304.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0958.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_305.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name video.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_306.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0960.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_307.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0961.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_308.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0964.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_309.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name SLEE SATURDAY.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_310.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0970.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_311.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0971.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_312.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0972.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_313.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0974.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_314.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0980.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_315.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0981.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_316.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0983.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_317.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0984.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_318.tif)
- Brad Lubman conducting soprano Heather Buck, bass Ethan Herschenfeld, Ensemble Signal, and Slee Sinfonietta in a performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0985.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_319.tif)
- Composer David Felder talking to conductor Brad Lubman at a rehearsal for Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0986.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_320.tif)
- Composer David Felder talking to conductor Brad Lubman at a rehearsal for Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0987.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_321.tif)
- Composer David Felder talking to conductor Brad Lubman at a rehearsal for Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0990.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_322.tif)
- Composer David Felder talking to conductor Brad Lubman at a rehearsal for Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0991.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_323.tif)
- Composer David Felder talking to conductor Brad Lubman at a rehearsal for Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0992.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_324.tif)
- Composer David Felder talking to conductor Brad Lubman at a rehearsal for Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0993.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_325.tif)
- Composer David Felder talking to conductor Brad Lubman at a rehearsal for Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0994.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_326.tif)
- Composer David Felder talking to conductor Brad Lubman at a rehearsal for Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0995.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_327.tif)
- Composer David Felder talking to conductor Brad Lubman at a rehearsal for Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0996.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_328.tif)
- Composer Augusta Read Thomas during a seminar at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_0998.tif Venue: Frank B. and Cameron Baird Music Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_329.tif)
- One of the images from the video by Olivier Pasquet projected during the performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1000.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_330.tif)
- Composer David Felder with J. T. Rinker, and Olivier Pasquet at the control consoles for a performance of his Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1005.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_331.tif)
- Composer David Felder with Matt Sargent, J. T. Rinker, Olivier Pasquet, and Patty Rihn at the control consoles for a performance of his Les quatre temps cardinaux at June in Buffalo 2015, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1006.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_332.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal before the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1013.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_333.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with video projection by Olivier Pasquet, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1017.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_334.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with video projection by Olivier Pasquet, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1019.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_335.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with video projection by Olivier Pasquet, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name Ensemble Signal and Slee Sinfonietta Lippes Concert Hall in Slee Hall.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_336.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with video projection by Olivier Pasquet, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name SLEE concert SEND SEND.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_337.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with video projection by Olivier Pasquet, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1021.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_338.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with video projection by Olivier Pasquet, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name SEND SEND SLEE.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_339.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with video projection by Olivier Pasquet, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1023.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_340.tif)
- Conductor Brad Lubman, soloists Heather Buck and Ethan Herschenfeld, and the Slee Sinfonietta with Ensemble Signal during the June in Buffalo 2015 performance of David Felder's Les quatre temps cardinaux with video projection by Olivier Pasquet, 2015-06-06, 1 color digital image (tiff format); Original file name _MG_1025.tif Venue: Frederick C. and Alice Slee Chamber Hall (State University of New York at Buffalo) (Image-file ubmu0074_341.tif)